<?xml version="1.0"?>

<game status="PO" id="2009_05_06_detmlb_chamlb_1" start_time="8:11" ampm="pm" time_zone="ET"  type="R" away_score="" home_score="" league="AL" series-code="" game-number="1">
    <ticketlink></ticketlink>
    <venueShort>U.S. Cellular Field</venueShort>
	<venueLong>U.S. Cellular Field</venueLong>
    <broadcast>
        <home>
        <tv>WCIU</tv>
        <radio>WSCR 670, WRTO 1200</radio>
</home>
        <away>
        <tv>FS-D HD</tv>
        <radio>WXYT 1270</radio>
</away>
    </broadcast>
    <probables>
	    
	<home>
		<player_id>279824</player_id>
		<useName>Mark</useName>
		<lastName>Buehrle</lastName>
		<number>56</number>
		<throwinghand>LHP</throwinghand>
		<wins>4</wins>
		<losses>0</losses>
		<era>3.30</era>
		<so>19</so>
		<report><![CDATA[Buehrle has now won four straight to start a season for the second time in his career and for the first time since 2002, after emerging victorious from Friday;s 4-3 win over Texas. Buehrle needed just 81 pitches to cover six innings, during which the southpaw allowed three runs on seven hits, while striking out two and not issuing a walk. He also was tagged for a home run by leadoff hitter Ian Kinsler. Buehrle has not faced the Tigers this season but has a 13-8 lifetime record against Detroit. Buehrle also holds a 70-40 career record with a 3.65 ERA at U.S. Cellular Field.]]></report>
	</home>

        
	<away>
		<player_id>451482</player_id>
		<useName>Armando</useName>
		<lastName>Galarraga</lastName>
		<number>58</number>
		<throwinghand>RHP</throwinghand>
		<wins>3</wins>
		<losses>1</losses>
		<era>3.07</era>
		<so>26</so>
		<report><![CDATA[It's still too early to determine anything about Galarraga's followup to his breakout 2008 season, but his last three outings have shown hints of pitching away from contact instead of towards it, as he did as a rookie. He has 11 walks over 16 innings in that stretch, including three over five innings in his most recent outing. The Indians, who had never hit him well, roughed him up for five runs on eight hits, but it was a walk to ninth man Kelly Shoppach in a four-run second inning that seemingly allowed his outing to unravel. Wednesday won't give him any break. He's 0-4 with a 5.23 ERA against the Twins, walking 20 batters over 32 2/3 innings.]]></report>
	</away>
	
	</probables>
    <previews>
        <home><url cid="200905064586340"><![CDATA[javascript:void(launchGameday({gid:'2009_05_06_detmlb_chamlb_1',mode:'preview',lurl:'/news/article.jsp?ymd=20090506&content_id=4586340&vkey=news_cws&fext=.jsp&c_id=cws'}))]]></url>
</home>
        <away>
</away>
    </previews>
    <recaps>
        <home>
</home>    
        <away>
</away>    
    </recaps>
    <wrap>
        <mlb>
</mlb>    
    </wrap>
    


<mlbtv_alt_feed_index>
</mlbtv_alt_feed_index>
</game>